{
    "questions": [{
            "problem": "In 3a + 6x expression, what are variables?",
            "choice1": "a and x",
            "choice2": "3a and 6x",
            "choice3": "3 and 6",
            "choice4": "3 and 8",
            "correctanswer": "1"
        },
        {
            "problem": "In the term 5x, the number \"5 \" is referred to as the:",
            "choice1": "Expression",
            "choice2": "Equation",
            "choice3": "Coefficient",
            "choice4": "Formula",
            "correctanswer": "3"
        },
        {
            "problem": "3a + 5n is an example of:",
            "choice1": "A formula",
            "choice2": "An equation",
            "choice3": "An expression",
            "choice4": "An identity",
            "correctanswer": "3"
        },
        {
            "problem": "5p – 14 = 36 is an example of:",
            "choice1": "A formula",
            "choice2": "An equation",
            "choice3": "An expression",
            "choice4": "An identity",
            "correctanswer": "2"
        },
        {
            "problem": "2 (n + m) = n + m +n + m:",
            "choice1": "An expression",
            "choice2": "A formula",
            "choice3": "An identity",
            "choice4": "An equation",
            "correctanswer": "3"
        },
        {
            "problem": "2b – 3 > 9 is an example of:",
            "choice1": "A formula",
            "choice2": "An equation",
            "choice3": "An inequality",
            "choice4": "An expression",
            "correctanswer": "3"
        },
        {
            "problem": "5<sup>2</sup>f + 5h<sup>5</sup> + 2gh is an example of:",
            "choice1": "An expression",
            "choice2": "An equation",
            "choice3": "An identity",
            "choice4": "A formula",
            "correctanswer": "1"
        },
        {
            "problem": "290 = 2x/6 is an example of:",
            "choice1": "An equation",
            "choice2": "An inequality",
            "choice3": "An identity",
            "choice4": "An expression",
            "correctanswer": "1"
        },
        {
            "problem": "5 < 5b – 15 < 65 is an example of:",
            "choice1": "A formula",
            "choice2": "An expression",
            "choice3": "An inequality",
            "choice4": "An equation",
            "correctanswer": "3"
        },
        {
            "problem": "3x + 3y = 3 (x + y) is an example of:",
            "choice1": "An equation",
            "choice2": "A formula",
            "choice3": "An expression",
            "choice4": "An identity",
            "correctanswer": "4"
        }

    ]
}